A Loud House Christmas is a family, comedy film directed by Jonathan Judge.
Lincoln Loud gears up for the ultimate Christmas, until he finds out that
most of his sisters have plans to be elsewhere for the big day.
Determined to remind his family that they all need to be together, Lincoln and his best friend
Clyde McBride embark on a mission to preserve the family’s holiday traditions.
Lincoln Loud, played by Wolfgang Schaeffer.
Clyde, played by Jahzir Bruno.
Lori Loud, played by Lexi DiBenedetto.
Leni Loud, played by Dora Dolphin.
Luna Loud, played by Sophia Woodward.
Luan Loud, played by Catherine Ashmore Bradley.
A Loud House Christmas is a 2021 American live-action Christmas comedy adventure family
television film based on the Nickelodeon animated series, The Loud House.
The film is directed by Jonathan Judge, written by Liz Maccie, and stars Wolfgang Schaeffer, Jahzir Bruno, Lexi DiBenedetto, Dora Dolphin, Sophia Woodward, Catherine Ashmore Bradley, Morgan McGill, Aubin Bradley, Lexi Janicek, Mia Allan,
Ella Allan, Charlotte Anne Tucker, Lainey Jane Knowles, and Muretta Moss while Catherine Taber and Brian Stepanek reprise their respective roles from the animated series as characters Katherine Mulligan and Lynn Loud Sr.
The first live-action work and second film in the overall franchise after The Loud House Movie, it aired
on Nickelodeon on November 26, 2021, and started streaming on Paramount+ the same day.
The film also serves as the backdoor pilot of the
sequel series, The Really Loud House.
A live-action television series sequel called The Really Loud House, featuring
several cast members from the film, premiered November 3, 2022.
The tone is lighthearted.